Fitting logistic regression models is
拟合逻辑回归模型
actually very similar to what you were doing in the last lesson,
实际上与上节课中
fitting linear regression models.
拟合线性回归模型非常类似
We can again use stats models to perform logistic regression on our dataset.
我们再次使用 statsmodels 对数据集进行逻辑回归
First, let's load our necessary libraries and the data as you see here.
首先我们加载必要的库和数据 正如你这里看到的
Similar to linear regression,
与线性回归类似
any variables that are categorical,
对于任何分类变量
we will want to change dummy variables.
我们想要改为虚拟变量
So, in this dataset that will be the day,
所以在这个数据集中
which you can see is labeled as weekend,
一些日期标记为工作日或周末
or weekday, and fraud which is either false or true.
诈骗要么为真 要么为假
So, we want to change those both the dummy variables,
所以我们把这些改为虚拟变量
and then we could fill in missing values and things like that.
然后我们填充缺失值 诸如此类
Although, I don't think there are any in this dataset.
虽然我认为这个数据集中存在这种情况
As you can see there is no missing values here,
正如你看到的 这里没有缺失值
and so we should create our dummy variables.
所以我们应当创建虚拟变量
And for now I'm just going to dummy the fraud variable,
这里我将要虚设诈骗 (fraud) 变量
and we'll use duration to predict fraud,
我们使用时长预测变量
and we will also add an intercept.
也会增加一个截距
So, here you can see we created those dummy variables,
所以这里你看到我们创建了这些虚拟变量
and I just created it with a zero for false up here,
我使用 0 表示这里的假
and then a one if it is true in this column.
如果这一列为真 使用 1 表示
And so I actually don't need that last one, we could drop it.
所以实际上不需要最后一个 我们可以删除
And, so that will be my data frame and let's go ahead and use stats models now.
这样就得到我的DataFrame 现在可以继续使用 statsmodels
And for logistic regression,
对于逻辑回归
instead of using the OLS,
我们不使用普通最小二乘法
we're going to use what's called the Logit.
而是使用评定 (Logit) 模型
And the first argument that we need to pass is the response,
我们需要传递的第一个参数值是反应变量
so we are going to pass.
所以我们即将完成
So, I am just going to pass this fraud and we should create our intercept.
所以我将要传递这组fraud数据 且应创造截距
So then similar to what you did in the last lesson,
实际上这与上节课内容相似
we will pass the intercept.
我们要传递截距
I do not know why my color highlighting is not working anymore.
我不知道为什么不能再使用高亮颜色了
And let's say we want to use duration,
那么说我们要使用时长
so we can create our model that way.
所以那样创建模型
And then again we can get a summary.
我们再次得到一个摘要
We need to fit it and then store that, cool.
我们需要进行拟合 然后存储起来 很棒
So, did the optimization and you can see we
所以进行最优化 你会发现
get similar output to what you saw in the previous lesson.
我们得到的输出结果与上节课你见到的很相似